https://urbancrazy.com/privacy-policy/

PRIVACY POLICY – EFFECTIVE 25th May 2018
On May 25th 2018, a change to data protection law will give you more control over how organisations use your personal data and privacy. UrbanCrazy takes data privacy seriously and we are committed to protecting your data. This privacy policy explains how we collect, store, use and share your data and personal information helping you understand what your rights are and what are responsibilities are in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 and the new General Data Protection Regulations 2018 (GDPR).
1. Transparency with how we use your data:
UrbanCrazy want you to have confidence in the way we use your data, and we have updated this Privacy Policy to reflect this.
2. Data security:
UrbanCrazy always takes steps and procedures to ensure that data is securely stored, but with the new regulations of 25th May 2018 we will be doing so with even more care.
All our electrical files and our computers themselves are protected with secure passwords and sensitive documents stored in a locked file cabinet.
3. Third parties:
All third parties that we use to process your held data have valid, clear and transparent data policies compliant with GDPR.
UrbanCrazy never have and never will sell your data to any third parties.
4. What we do with collated data:
UrbanCrazy collects personal data for to provide a service to our clientele. This includes a person or a company that is (or has been) subscribed to our mailing list; submitted an online enquiry form directly from one of our websites; in direct contact with UrbanCrazy through email; or engaging with us on one of our social media platforms.
We email our subscribers newsletters with offers on deals that are only for relevant to specific clients and only for the legitimate purposes stated.
You can check the information that we hold about you by emailing us or contacting us. If you find any inaccuracies, we will amend/delete them immediately as appropriate.
5. What data we collect:
UrbanCrazy collects only the information from you upon enquiry to enable us to provide you with the fulfilment of your order.
6. Consent:
UrbanCrazy always ask permission before adding any content to our website whether the content by imagery, photographs, quotes or testimonials.
We will not contact you in the future unless you have given us your consent. We will always give you the opportunity to refuse or opt out of any marketing email at any point now or in the future.
We will never collect sensitive information about you without your explicit consent.
About us
UrbanCrazy (mobile) Ltd trading as UrbanCrazy Ltd and UrbanCrazy is a company registered in England and Wales (since December 2002) with registration number 4596573 and registered address: Devonshire House, 582 Honeypot Lane, Stanmore, Middx, HA7 1JS
UrbanCrazy own and operate game brands: UrbanCrazy; PongCrazy; BallDropCrazy; and DartsCrazy
If you have any questions/comments about privacy or wish to view our full Company Privacy Policy, please contact us.
Contact Us
If you can’t find what you’re looking for, or if you have any further questions about our courses, games or accessories, please do get in contact with us via our ‘Contact us’ page; we would love to help.
